在forecasefragment类中，我们更改了
In the forecast fragment class, we modify the
onOptionsItemSelected方法。当Refresh菜单项被选择，
onOptionsItemSelected method. When the Refresh menu item is selected,
我们创建了一个新的FetchWeatherTask，并且我们调用
we create a new FetchWeatherTask and then we call
execute。尽管调用不再阻塞UI线程
execute on it. While the call is no longer
因为这是AsyncTask，
blocking the UI thread because it's an AsyncTask, the
应用仍然会崩溃。如果你查看日志，
app will still crash. If we check the logs,
我们会看到在这应用崩溃了。
we see that the app crashed. This time though,
这是一个security的异常。它说权限被拒绝，并且问
with a security expression. It says Permission denied and
是不是没有申请INTERNET权限。确实，
ask if you're missing the INTERNET permission or not. And indeed,
我们没申请INTERNET权限，因此我们需要申请它。
we are missing the INTERNET permission, so we need to request it.